# Kelly McCann

product designer & strategist

678.296.0465 www.kellymccann.design kellymccann91@gmail.com

### profile

Designer, strategist, and researcher with development chops. Facilitator, relationship builder, systems thinker.

My background lies in Product: UX/UI design, front-end dev, user research, and strategy. I care about elegant, intuitive, and scalable builds, putting users first, scoping clear acceptance criteria, and cultivating collaborative relationships across teams.



### certifications

SCRUM Alliance - Certified Product Owner Hubspot Academy - Growth Driven Design Gymnasium - Atomic Design & Pattern Lab Writing for Web & Mobile Dynamic Yield - Certified Engineer

### education

University of Massachusetts, Boston -BA in Art, Studio Focus, Deans List & 4.0 GPA

## experience

### thoughtbot

consulting

Product Strategist & Designer

3/2019 - 2/2020

Advise clients on design strategy, risk and product scope. Facilitate Design Sprints, prioritize feature builds, conduct user testing, create prototypes. Conceptualize and iterate upon visual designs and implement front-end development. Present ongoing research findings, design, and development work.

#### **Richline Digital**

eCommerce

UI / UX Manager

4/2018 - 3/2019

Product design, user research, scope frontend builds, oversee content management. Manage brand launches and CMS migrations, liaise with stakeholders to scope product strategy.

Content Manager

12/2017 - 4/2018

Manage content and website updates, create CMS documentation, generate mocks and wireframes.

#### MIT Office of Digital Learning

edTech

UX Researcher, Content & Communications Manager 10/2016 - 10/2017

Conduct and report upon user research, maintain customer engagement endeavors, manage CMS, content generation, social media marketing. Contract role.

#### Selventa

bioTech

Web Designer / Developer

3/2015 - 6/2016

All frontend design and development. Manage client relationships, scope acceptance criteria.

Assistant Project Manager &

8/2014 - 3/2015

**Executive Assistant** 

Generate mocks/wireframes, manage office build-out and office operations, liaise with clients.